He threw us out like garbage.
Stripped me of everything.
Why should I care
if he lives or dies?
He's a cold-blooded bastard.
I'm doing this for you.
Yes, he kicked you out.
But you are still the
rightful heir of House Carter.
Those lands, that title, everything, it belongs to you.
Only you.
I don't want any of that worthless junk.
But I will not
let that scheming half-brother
of yours steal
what belongs to you.
Not while I'm still breathing!
So my pathetic brother
still won't break the engagement?
He wants to humiliate himself.
I'm happy to give it to him.
Get yourself ready.
At the wedding,
I'll announce that you are my real husband.
I'll make Severin the laughingstock of all Emeraldstone.
Come on, you
two grew up together.
That's pretty harsh, even for you.
If he wants to cling
on like a stray dog,
he deserves what's coming.
I can't wait for that wedding.
And the second the
old man stops breathing,
everything in House Carter becomes mine.
Not only that.
Oh, it's better than that.
The Sovereign Sanctum
has promised to elevate
me above the Four Great Families.
I will rise
as a new goddess.
Then you better make
sure you show proper...
gratitude to Steward Jeyn.
Once we lock in that connection,
every noble across Golantis will
bend the knee to us.
The demonic energy
has ravaged the Count's organs.
Is there...
any hope?
There is only one
man capable of saving you.
Who?
The one who has
withdrawn from the world.
The Godfather.